

# Full Stack Web Developer

39 Ondo street Ibadan, Oyo State, Nigeria, Ohio, 200221 babtol235@gmail.com +2347041147115

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/tolulope-

babatunde-8b4266156

Github: https://github.com/tolulopejoshua Portfolio: https://tolulopejoshua.github.io

I am a Full Stack developer with over 3 years experience working as a freelance developer. I work frequently with React, Vue, Nextls, and Nodels. I am passionate about learning latest developments and technologies, and creating exceptional solutions.

# **Professional Experience**

## Full Stack Web Developer

GIP Library | May 2021 - Present

Developed a full-stack modern admin dashboard with Nextls front-end, Nodels back-end REST api, Mongo database, and AWS simple storage solution.

Developed and deployed a Nodejs application with CRUD functionality for creating and updating library resources.

Collaborated with designers and dev teams to design and implement user-friendly interfaces for external users.

#### Full Stack Developer

Fiverr, Nigeria | February 2019 - April 2021

- Developed an E-commerce website for a car dealership business using ReactIs for single-page interface and state management, Firebase for user authentication, Sanity for data management, and Stripe for payments.
- Developed a marketing website for a Fashion store with modern interface and advanced cart management functionality.
- · Created user-friendly interfaces that enable users to understand how to use complex technical products.
- Implemented effective security protocols and data protection measures.
- Designed and implemented backend infrastructure and APIs that adhere to best practises.

#### **Education**

## Bachelor of Technology - BTech in Physics

Federal University of Technology Akure at Nigeria | January 2010 - January 2015

# **Key Skills**

- Technical skills include css, html, javascript, typescript, reactjs, nodejs, sql/nosql databases, cloud computing.
- Troubleshooting skills for reviewing and fixing code and other software issues.
- · Good understanding of web application security, and session management.
- REST server architecture and automated testing.